I made your favorite:
pizza bagels!
(Penny:)Pink wine and pizza bagels?
(Penny:)It's like eighth grade
all over again.
(Penny:)I am so lucky to have you.
(Leonard:)Well, now be careful,
these are hot.
I-I could explain
the thermodynamics
(Leonard:)of why the cheese seems
hotter than the crust,
(Leonard:)but instead, I'm gonna
keep it to myself.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Penny:)You always know what not to say.
(Penny:)I just, I can't believe
you did all this.
(Leonard:)Well, you know,
(Leonard:)it's easy to take each
other for granted and
(Leonard:)I never want to do
that to you, because
(Leonard:)your love,
(Leonard:)it's like a river.
(Leonard:)It's peaceful and deep.
(Leonard:)Your soul is,
it's like a secret
that I never could keep.
(Penny:)You did not just
quote an NSYNC song.
I quoted your favorite
NSYNC song.
(Penny:)Oh...
(Amy:)Mm.
(Leonard:)Damn.
(Leonard:)I burped so hard,
I died in my game.